Now, I don't know about y'all, but I find it real funny style that these folks who have engaged ardently in genocide are just heading out on book tours.
Also, what are they writing about in these books?
What a value can we learn from Karine Jumpier at this point?
She's a switch sider.
She used to be all about the people and then she got all about the Benjamins.
What are we learning from Kamala Harris at this point?
She's failed two campaigns.
She was committed to the system before as a top cop.
What are we learning?
You know what we need to learn?
The ways in which we can move beyond the limitations that have been given and put in place by this empire.
I'm on a book tour.
My book is a little different than whatever they write.
Actually, it's a lot different.
And my work is too.
I know a lot of y'all oftentimes say things like, well, Amanda, if you have such a problem with politics, then why don't you become a politician?
Amanda, why aren't you in the streets?
Why aren't you organizing?
I am a different effort.
Because the thing about it is a lot of folks don't realize you can elect all the right people and you can work with the best organizers.
But if the mind ain't right, then nothing is ever going to change.
Because the system that the right people is going into is wrong.
And the organizing the organizers are doing will become unorganized.
We need food.
We need water.
We need shelter.
We need many things that this society isn't giving us.
And we also need the ability to gain those things from within us.
We need to decolonize and rewire.
And that is my work.
That is the work of this new book, What Would the Ancestors Say?
And that is the work of all of my edutainment.
But I know how to do it because I did it for myself.
And I want to help you do it too.
Through the arts, through humor, through all the things.
In my own unique Amanda Seals way.
So come on out.
I'll be in San Diego tonight.
I will be in Los Angeles.
You can get the live stream tickets at amandaseals.com.
I'm going to be in Seattle.
Then I'm going to be in Detroit.
Then I'm going to be in Chicago.
And I hope that you're going to be there.
Because sitting around and listening to folks who have used their mind, body, and soul to aid in the expansion of the United States tyranny.
Baby, that ain't worth your time.
And that's not going to help you fight for your own mind, body, and soul against United States tyranny.
I'll bet both of them could Tisha, so having a white partner helped them climb the ladder empire.
Ba-dum-bum!
Head to amandaseals.com and get your tickets to the live stream performance and release of my new book,
What Would The Ancestors Say, on November 8th.
Also check out When I'll Be In Your City with my book tour.
See you then.
Pop, pop!